



HTML/CSS, JavaScript-jQuery, Bootstrap, Materialize



Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Adobe Creative Cloud



Axure, Balsamiq, InVision, Sketch, Justinmind, Framer.js

I'm a **Digital Product Designer** with 3+ years of experience designing delightful web & mobile solutions. My passion lies in bridging the gap between **Innovative Technology** and **Social Impact** through the power of **Design**.



**EXPERIENCE** 

### **Interaction Design Intern**

**GE Energy Connections, Redmond, WA** | June 2016 – September 2016

- Primary project involved the redesign of **e-terrasimulator Dispatcher Training Simulator** a software used by electrical grid operators to simulate power distribution environments for training purposes.
- In alignment with a corporate initiative to redesign legacy software based on modern usability & interface design standards, the project entails the creation & design of new features & functionality as well as overall user experience improvements.

## **UX/UI Designer**

Joomla, Seattle, WA | June 2015 - June 2016

- Worked with various volunteers around the world on a redesign (usability & interface) project for the next web versions of Joomla CMS, Joomla 3.5 & 3.6 (release in March & July 2016 15% increase in user retention).
- Participated in various web & mobile redesign projects for **Joomla.org & Joomla.com** Joomla's primary websites as part of an initiative to improve user sign up rates as well as branding.

## **User Experience Designer**

VnExpress, Seattle (Remote), WA | September 2013 – June 2015

- Helped design the information architecture, interaction, and visual for VnExpress International (release in June 2015 20+ active million users) the English version of VnExpress, the most popular online news websites in Vietnam.
- Lead a design initiative for VnExpress Mobile (release in September 2014 50+ active million users) the site's mobile app
  (iOS & Android). Ideated a concept through user research and took it through multiple design & test iterations before
  proposing to development.

### **Marketing Analyst**

ComputeNext, Bellevue, WA | March 2014 - June 2015

- Engaged with Managed Service Providers, IT Resellers/Distributors, and System Integrators around the adoption of ComputeNext's Global Cloud Marketplace – an end-to-end cloud sourcing, deployment, and management platform.
- Supported the UX team in conducting user research activities, as well as usability tests, to involve partners & clients in the development of the product.

EDUCATION

# MS in Information Management (User Experience Research & Design)

University of Washington, Seattle | September 2015 – Present

**BA in International Studies** (International Political Economy & Business)

University of Washington, Seattle | September 2012 – June 2014





